All right, so what did you do?
很好   然后你又做了什么
What did you do?
后来你是怎么做的
Third time, I got bent.
第三次   我被撞了一下
The...Third time of what, Jack?
第三次什么   杰克
Third slow, everything went sideways.
第三次慢下来   一切都歪过去了
And then it stopped, then I jumped.
接着车停下了  我就跳下了
I got it, buddy. I got it.
我明白了   孩子   我明白了
5409 call.
5409号呼叫
Dispatch. Listen carefully. We have a rough location.
立即派遣警员   仔细听好 我们只有大致地点
All right. Uh, south on Elm.
好的 呃   埃尔姆路南段
Three stop signs pass the junction with beach.
经过三个停车标识   靠近海滩的交叉路口
Look for a garden shed with a skylight.
寻找一个带天窗的后院棚屋
Also check the most recent satellite images for a red pick-up in the driveway.
用最新卫星图找一辆停车道上的红色皮卡车
5409 on route.
5409号在路上了
Unbelievable.
难以置信